(Stuart:)Thanks, Leonard.
(Stuart:)What is that thing anyway?
(Howard:)You don't know what this is?
(Leonard:)- No.
- Good, get out.
(Raj:)Be afraid of Penny. Nice, very crafty.
(Leonard:)It wasn't bad advice.
It just wasn't particularly helpful.
(Sheldon:)For what it's worth, my mother says
that when we deceive for personal gain...
(Sheldon:)...we make Jesus cry.
(Sheldon:)All right, what if we use this two-inch PVC
to reinforce the center cross-support?
(Howard:)No good. I mean, it might work
for the Japanese and the Americans...
(Howard:)...but have you seen the size
of the Russians they got up there?
(Howard:)This thing has to hold up
against a hearty potato-based diet.
(Leonard:)I feel terrible.
(Howard:)Maybe if you were helping,
you'd feel better about yourself.